CONFIDENCE U. DIKE

10 Hill Street, Apt 9B, Newark, New Jersey, 07102 | Cell: (347) 938-3702 | Email: uc.dike44@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE:

Energetic, dedicated, and detailed-oriented individual with more than five years of Administrative Professional experience who excels at prioritizing, completing multiple tasks simultaneously and following through to achieve organizational goals. Emphasizes on maintaining the utmost confidentiality with any line of business. Also works well with others, deadline driven, fast learner with strong drive to succeed within the company.

KEY SKILLS:

- Office Management
- Problem Solving
- Excellent Communication and Interpersonal
- Time Management

- Customer Service
- Planning and Organizational
- Microsoft Word, Excel, Power-point, Outlook, Adobe Acrobat

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Administrative/Customer Service Team Lead

IKEA, Elizabeth, NJ

- Consistently improve customer satisfaction through expert solutions of conflict and service concerns
- Prepare and review operational reports and schedules to ensure accuracy and efficiency
- Conduct training and orientation for new hires
- Support in developing service procedures, policies and standards
- Coordinate an orderly workflow according to priorities
- Provide support to resources control towards achieving qualitative and quantitative targets
- Keeping abreast of management changes and business developments

Administrative Assistant, Golden Dome Athletic Center Rutgers The State University of New Jersey, Newark NJ

January 2012- August 2017

April 2016 - Present

- Organized and increased health awareness initiatives and program
- Processed new members to the gymnasium and register students and clients for intramural and recreational classes
- Provided administrative support including answering the main line and screening calls
- Provided management support in monitoring attendance and payroll related issues
- Performed administrative and clerical functions such as faxing, scanning, copying and operate other office equipment
- Provided onboarding orientation, training and work schedules for student workers
- · Provided updated student employee files to document personnel actions and to provide information for payroll uses
- Managed computed wages, and recorded data for use in payroll processing
- Prepared and file reports of accidents and injuries at establishment

Youth Ambassador/Volunteer

The TESS Foundation of Africa

August 2015 - April 2016

- Represented the Tess Foundation in a professional manner at community outreach programs, health fairs and cultural festivals
- Assisted in defining clear strategy for Tess Academy Education initiatives along with developing protocols and procedures
- Organized fund-raising events in the community to educate others about the Tess's vision, mission, and values
- Responsible for mentoring young adults virtually and in person
- Delivered and developed creative key messaging to engage students, supporters, and sponsor

EDUCATION:

Master of Public Administration (M.P.A)

May 2016

Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey, Newark NJ Bachelor of Science(B.Sc.) Criminal Justice

October 2013

Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey, Newark NJ